Dennis Williams

Full Stack Engineer

Manteca, California, 95336, United States

pegasusxnwn@gmail.com

https://github.com/pegasussx

PROFILE

A full stack engineer with 8 years of experience in software development and handled multiple projects from ideation to development, maintenance and ultimately client acquisition. Expert in modern programming languages, frameworks and databases. Xiang loves to think everything simple, and avoid duplication, enjoy working collaboratively with co-workers. He has passion in problem solving and critical thinking.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Full Stack Engineer (Full-time remote)

Seidat Oy August 2021 - September 2022 https://seidat.com

Senior Web Developer who was working on Meteor.js + React.js project based on the Nx architectured project. Resolved several technical problems and integrated Pipedrive and other third party services into the existing platform. Worked under very strict code review. At the same time, I reviewed other pull requests and was able to improve my skills efficiently.

Smart Contract Developer (Part-time remote)

HawkAyes NFTs November 2021 - March 2022 https://www.hawkayes.com

Side project of the Jobhub Group, enjoyed smart contract development while building the NFT Marketplace. Final goal is just publishing the De-Fi solution along with our token and NFTs. 20+ contracts were completed in the beta version, with unique tokenomics and wow-factor features. As an experienced engineer led web3.js integration stuff with detailed guidelines under the strict review.

Technical Advisor & Lead Developer (Full-time remote)

Linalgo February 2018 - April 2021 https://linalgo.com https://linflash.com https://app.linflash.com

Worked as a structural design engineer for numerous projects and as the Senior Backend Engineer for over 3 years. Created the main website and multiple mobile applications using modern technologies. Introduced new technologies and served as a presenter of the company mentoring system. Developed & worked on Amazon Web Services, where the services were used as the company's main infrastructure area. Not only the websites, but also mobile applications, along with a supporting admin panel.

HARD SKILLS

React.js / Next.js / Angular / Vue.js / Nuxt.js / Svelt.js / Gatsby / Meter.js

HTML5 / CSS3

JavaScript / TypeScript / PHP / Node.js

Java / Golang / Python

Express.js / Nest.js / Flask / Django / Spring Framework / Laravel

MySQL / MongoDB / PostgreSQL / GraphQL / Firebase

Smart Contract / Solidity / Rust

CosmosSDK / Tendermint / Chain Development

Git / SVN / BitBucket

Docker / Kerberos

Jenkins / CircleCI / Bamboo

AWS / Heroku / Netlify

React.js Developer (Full-time remote)

Taks Inc December 2016 - May 2018

https://taks.io

https://apps.microsoft.com/store/detail/taks-app/9N9L70HNK6BC?hl=en-us&gl=us https://apps.apple.com/us/app/taks-organize-lifes-projects/id1475329362?ls=1

Designed and developed a distributed solution for a Ticket management service using React.js and Java Spring framework. Developed an Android/iOS application available on the Play Store and App Store. Published desktop application which can be run on different platforms, and published it to the Microsoft App Store. Implemented a web application that allowed third-party vendors to integrate and manage their calendars in a single place, with controllable widgets.

EDUCATION

University of California-Berkeley, California

April 2011 - March 2015

Bachelor's degree of Engineering (Computer Science and Design)

As a student of Computer Science and Engineering, I've learned the basic principles and methods to develop software systems and web services, and how to take the user perspective into account.

In addition, I've extended my knowledge and skills, I've also learned how to apply these to solve specific problems.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Web Development Professional, Application Developer, 2018
- Java Development Certified Professional, 2017

SOFT SKILLS

- Simply Thinking
- Avoid Duplication
- · Problem Solving
- Communication
- Creativity

LANGUAGE

Gaming

Traveling

English
Chinese
новву
Table Tennis
Market Researching